(Sheldon:)Flaming Spittoon.
(Sheldon:)And for the record,
I'm very disappointed in you, cowpokes.
(Sheldon:)We're playing our inaugural round
of Wild West and witches...
(Sheldon:)...and I'm the only one who bothered
to dress for the occasion.
(Sheldon:)Patooie.
(Howard:)We're not wearing cowboy hats,
Sheldon. It looks ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)And I suppose my boots and spurs
are ridiculous too?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
Incredibly so.
(Sheldon:)Did it look ridiculous
when we got the Satanimals pack...
(Sheldon:)...and I dressed up as a Beelzebobcat?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
Incredibly so.
(Sheldon:)All right, fine. Let's just play.
(Leonard:)We should go easy on him.
Amy's out with Stuart tonight.
(Howard:)Wait a minute. Are you telling me...
(Howard:)...that Sheldon's patented blend
of condescension and no sex...
(Howard:)...isn't enough to hold on to a woman?
(Sheldon:)Cluck. Cluck. Cluck.
What are we, ladies at a quiIting bee?